(Silence; Operating Room Area)
=Stand Up for Love=
=Episode 14=
I made you my dog back then.
And I can do the same now.
What are you waiting for?
Beat him to death!
(What a shame.)
(You never got to know)
(that you would die by my hand.)
Beat him to death!
Break his legs!
Haotian!
No!
His ears!
Cut off his ears!
It's you.
(Haotian, you're back.)
(You love fish, don't you?)
(I bought some for you today.)
(And your favorite meat, too.)
(Today,)
(I'll make braised pork for you.)
(I even bought fresh fish today.)
(You're going to love it.)
(I learned the recipe online.)
(What's wrong?)
(Haotian.)
(Three.)
(Two.)
(One.)
(Run!)
(Zhang Haotian!)
(What kind of dump is this?)
(Is this even fit for people
to live in?)
(Zhang Haotian, get out here!)
(There's another match this afternoon.)
(This time, you will compete
with a German shepherd dog.)
(Be there on time.)
(What the hell?)
(What are you waiting for?)
(Kill him!)
(Kill her!)
You're still alive?
I thought you'd turn to ashes by now.
If someone hadn't called the police,
I really would turn to ashes.
You plotted this all along,
and went to such lengths
to lure Chen Ping into a trap...
It was all to get revenge on me.
The deeper the love,
the deeper the hatred.
Zhao Mai.
How much did you love me?
Yes.
I loved you once.
I gave you everything I had.
Everything I did for you...
I don't regret it.
No? Then why did you find Wang
to take revenge on me?
Zhang Haotian.
For these ten years,
I've told myself countless times
to let you go,
and to let myself go.
But I couldn't.
Every time I close my eyes,
I see the look in your eyes
before you left.
I have always treated people sincerely.
But you
made me question who I was.
When you gave me your love,
did you ever ask if I wanted it?
What you gave me was never
what I wanted.
I was like
a dog trapped in a cage by all of you.
♪That burns you like the cold♪
♪Ain't no fire, fire♪
I want you to repay
all the pain you caused me back then.
Zhang Haotian.
I grew up in an orphanage.
But you
were worse off than an orphan.
You grew up enduring people's
contempt and humiliation.
You had enough of being poor.
You were terrified of being poor again.
♪Caught in the madness♪
Back then,
you were played like a dog.
Wasn't it all just for money?
For money,
what's wrong with acting like a dog?
I didn't care.
Is this your last desperate struggle?
If thinking this way makes you
feel better,
then keep believing it.
I'm going to save Chen Ping.
I'm going to save him.
♪Ain't no fire, fire♪
(A Dog)
♪Listen, the wind chimes softly whisper♪
♪I should forget you♪
♪But I have the will,
yet not the strength♪
♪To carry on♪
♪The scenery you once longed to see♪
♪You no longer have the strength♪
♪You want me to go there for you♪
♪I look up and see a hollow sky♪
♪Your freedom♪
♪Has become my cage♪
♪My hand brushes over your smile
in the photograph♪
♪This glass of wine is filled
with sorrow♪
♪I look up at the beautiful night sky♪
♪You told me♪
♪I would shine like a star♪
♪But you forgot to teach me♪
♪How to live without you♪
♪I look up at the starry sky♪
♪So hazy and blurred♪